http://gemmfg.com/privacy-policy.html

Precision Parts Drawn In PartnershipRequest A Quote(203) 574-1466
sales@gemmfg.com
Home About Us Engineering Example Projects
Electrical Conduit Metal FerrulesStainless Steel ValvesBrass Electrical Connector ComponentsNickel Plated Brass Electrical ComponentsBrass Button AssembliesBlasting CapsStainless Steel Temperature SensorsValve Cores
Products
Gem Manufacturing Metal Eyelets Gem Manufacturing Omni-Tact Sockets
Our Processes Quality Industries Served Videos Contact Us
Services & CapabilitiesIn-Line Transfer & Progressive Deep Drawn Metal StampingCNC Milling & CNC Turning ServicesWire Electrical Discharge
Machining (EDM)
Tweet
Privacy PolicyGem Manufacturing respects your privacy and our site visitors' information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.Information Collected
If you request or submit information to us by sending an Email via sales@gemmfg.com or by filling out a "contact" form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your Email and other information will not be sold to any third party.Information Collected by Others
This notice addresses only Gem Manufacturing's website policy, and does not apply to sites that users access via links from our site. Gem Manufacturing is not responsible for the information collecting policies of other sites, for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, or for the information or content contained therein. Often, links to other websites are provided solely on the basis that they may contain useful information for our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.Cookies
Gem Manufacturing's website does not use cookies.Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information
If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an Email with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information
Gem Manufacturing may disclose information when legally compelled to do so: when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so or for the protection of our legal rights.Periodic Policy Changes
Please note that Gem Manufacturing reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.This policy statement is made in the name of Gem Manufacturing and is effective as of March 4, 2015. This statement does not create an agreement between Gem Manufacturing and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.Contact Us:
Gem Manufacturing
78 Brookside Rd.
E-mail: sales@gemmfg.comwww.GEMMFG.comPrivacy PolicySitemapCatalog Index
Copyright © 2015 GEM Manufacturing, All Rights ReservedSite created by Thomas Web Solutions and Powered by Navigator Platform
